<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GeoNAVI on GEONAVI LAB</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/geonavi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GeoNAVI on GEONAVI LAB</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/geonavi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysing and visualising mobility vulnerability and recovery across Florida neighbourhoods: a case study of Hurricane Ian</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/12/analysing-and-visualising-mobility-vulnerability-and-recovery-across-florida-neighbourhoods-a-case-study-of-hurricane-ian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/12/analysing-and-visualising-mobility-vulnerability-and-recovery-across-florida-neighbourhoods-a-case-study-of-hurricane-ian/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/21681376.2024.2369550&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Regional Studies, Regional Science&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Effective hurricane preparedness and response demand a thorough understanding of the impact on mobility patterns. While existing studies have explored mobility disruptions caused by hurricanes, very few have delved into the impact, considering both mobility vulnerability and recovery, on a state level. Utilising mobile phone location data, this research examines the mobility patterns of Florida residents throughout Hurricane Ian. The findings reveal that the hurricane profoundly disturbed the mobility patterns of Floridians. The state experienced a maximum average daily mobility reduction of 63.41%, with certain neighbourhoods coming to a complete standstill at 100% cessation in mobility. On average, Florida neighbourhoods needed 2.61 days for mobility recovery, though this period stretched to as long as 92 days in the most severely affected areas. The bivariate map highlights a prevailing trend: neighbourhoods with prolonged recovery periods also witnessed more substantial reductions in mobility. This dual disadvantage underscores the critical need for increased focus on these neighbourhoods. Furthermore, our findings highlight the significance of factoring in forecasted hurricane paths when analysing mobility impacts, as we noted more substantial effects on neighbourhoods along the predicted trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu is promoted to Associate Professor with tenure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/02/dr-yujie-hu-is-promoted-to-associate-professor-with-tenure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/07/02/dr-yujie-hu-is-promoted-to-associate-professor-with-tenure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu is promoted to Associate Professor with tenure at the University of Florida. Congratulations to Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://geog.ufl.edu/faculty/ryan/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Sadie Ryan&lt;/a&gt; and Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://geog.ufl.edu/faculty/hamerlinck/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Gaby Hamerlinck&lt;/a&gt;, too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:image {&#34;id&#34;:1259,&#34;sizeSlug&#34;:&#34;large&#34;,&#34;linkDestination&#34;:&#34;none&#34;} --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-large&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returners and explorers dichotomy in the face of natural hazards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/06/08/returners-and-explorers-dichotomy-in-the-face-of-natural-hazards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/06/08/returners-and-explorers-dichotomy-in-the-face-of-natural-hazards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a class=&#34;anchor anchor-secondary publication-title-link&#34; title=&#34;Go to Journal of Transport Geography on ScienceDirect&#34; href=&#34;https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-64087-4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;anchor-text-container&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;anchor-text&#34;&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding human mobility patterns amid natural hazards is crucial for enhancing urban emergency responses and rescue operations. Existing research on human mobility has delineated two primary types of individuals: returners, who exhibit a tendency to frequent a limited number of locations, and explorers, characterized by a more diverse range of movement across various places. Yet, whether this mobility dichotomy endures in the context of natural hazards remains underexplored. This study addresses this gap by examining anonymized high-resolution mobile phone location data from Lee County, Florida residents, aiming to unravel the dynamics of these distinct mobility groups throughout different phases of Hurricane Ian. The results indicate that returners and explorers maintained their distinct mobility characteristics even during the hurricane, showing increased separability. Before the hurricane, returners favored shorter trips, while explorers embarked on longer journeys, a trend that continued during the hurricane. However, the hurricane heightened people’s inclination to explore, leading to a notable increase in longer-distance travel for both groups, likely influenced by evacuation considerations. Spatially, both groups exhibited an uptick in trips towards the southern regions, away from the hurricane’s path, particularly converging on major destinations such as Miami, Fort Lauderdale, Naples, and West Palm Beach during the hurricane.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations to our 2024 graduates!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/05/06/congratulations-to-our-2024-graduates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/05/06/congratulations-to-our-2024-graduates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We wanted to congratulate our lab members who recently graduated: &lt;a href=&#34;https://geog.ufl.edu/grad-students/jinpengwang/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Jinpeng Wang&lt;/a&gt; on getting a Master&#39;s Degree in Geography and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/cora-crytzer-4b507120b/overlay/about-this-profile/&#34;&gt;Cora Crytzer&lt;/a&gt; on graduating Cum Laude with a Bachelors degree in Economics and a minor in Geography!&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:image {&#34;id&#34;:1225,&#34;sizeSlug&#34;:&#34;large&#34;,&#34;linkDestination&#34;:&#34;none&#34;} --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-large&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:image {&#34;id&#34;:1226,&#34;sizeSlug&#34;:&#34;large&#34;,&#34;linkDestination&#34;:&#34;none&#34;} --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-large&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu gave a talk at UF Epidemiology Seminar Series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/05/02/dr-yujie-hu-gave-a-talk-at-uf-epidemiology-seminar-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/05/02/dr-yujie-hu-gave-a-talk-at-uf-epidemiology-seminar-series/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu was invited by University of Florida&#39;s Epidemiology Department to present his research on modeling of commuting flows, travel distance, and encounter networks. Watch recording &lt;a href=&#34;https://epidemiology.phhp.ufl.edu/seminars/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GeoNAVI lab is rocking at the 2024 AAG annual conference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/04/19/the-geonavi-lab-is-rocking-at-the-2024-aag-annual-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/04/19/the-geonavi-lab-is-rocking-at-the-2024-aag-annual-conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Graduate students Yue Jing, Md. Shaharier Alam, Jinpeng Wang, and Zeyu He present at the 2024 AAG annual conference in Hawaii.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:image {&#34;id&#34;:1266,&#34;sizeSlug&#34;:&#34;large&#34;,&#34;linkDestination&#34;:&#34;none&#34;} --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-large&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right of Way: Race, Class, and the Silent Epidemic of Pedestrian Deaths in America by Angie Schmitt (Book Review)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/04/10/right-of-way-race-class-and-the-silent-epidemic-of-pedestrian-deaths-in-america-by-angie-schmitt-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/04/10/right-of-way-race-class-and-the-silent-epidemic-of-pedestrian-deaths-in-america-by-angie-schmitt-book-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New book review published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://muse.jhu.edu/pub/12/article/883673/summary&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Southeastern Geographer&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling spatial mismatch in childcare supply and demand: An excess commuting analysis of home-to-childcare distance in subsidized families</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/03/06/unveiling-spatial-mismatch-in-childcare-supply-and-demand-an-excess-commuting-analysis-of-home-to-childcare-distance-in-subsidized-families/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/03/06/unveiling-spatial-mismatch-in-childcare-supply-and-demand-an-excess-commuting-analysis-of-home-to-childcare-distance-in-subsidized-families/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a class=&#34;anchor anchor-secondary publication-title-link&#34; title=&#34;Go to Journal of Transport Geography on ScienceDirect&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0966692324000383&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;anchor-text-container&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;anchor-text&#34;&gt;Journal of Transport Geography&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; The distance between homes and childcare providers serves as a crucial factor in evaluating accessibility and equity in early childhood education. Spatial mismatch between childcare demand and supply is suggested when families opt for facilities further than the nearest available options, a situation scarcely scrutinized in existing literature, especially among under-six children from economically disadvantaged backgrounds. To fill this research gap, this study leverages the excess commuting analysis to delve into the extent of extended travel undertaken by subsidized families to access childcare services. Utilizing real enrollment data from the Florida&amp;rsquo;s School Readiness program, it quantifies the disparity between actual and shortest possible commuting distances, investigating the tendencies of low-income families to forgo nearby providers for their young children. Furthermore, the research probes into age-related disparities in excess commuting, examining to what degree childcare facilities are more conveniently located for certain age groups compared to others. The analysis unveils substantial spatial mismatch in subsidized childcare, with a significant portion of low-income families choosing more distant providers, resulting in a 51.3% surplus in commuting distance. It also highlights a noticeable age-dependent trend in this mismatch: parents of infants face a dual disadvantage with longer commutes, compared to families with five-year-olds who have closer access to providers. The findings advocate for policy reforms that address these disparities, enhancing the efficiency and equity of childcare resource allocation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Complex Network Analysis of Commuting Efficiency: Urban Connectivity, Hierarchy, and Labor Market</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/01/22/multiscale-complex-network-analysis-of-commuting-efficiency-urban-connectivity-hierarchy-and-labor-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/01/22/multiscale-complex-network-analysis-of-commuting-efficiency-urban-connectivity-hierarchy-and-labor-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/24694452.2023.2284296&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Annals of the American Association of Geographers&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; This study employs the 2012 to 2016 commuting flows of Florida to reexamine excess commuting (EC) through multiscale complex network analysis. The results reveal significant discrepancies in urban connectivity, hierarchy, and labor market geography between the actual (ACN) and optimal commuting networks (OCN). Compared to ACN, OCN illustrates an overly simplified and isolated polycentric commuting system. This is evident through reduced overall network connectivity, a restructured centrality distribution pattern, and fragmented community divisions. Consequently, these results underscore the importance of delving into the economic implications of commuting within the conventional EC framework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting hurricane evacuation for local neighborhoods across a metropolitan region</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/11/07/predicting-hurricane-evacuation-for-local-neighborhoods-across-a-metropolitan-region/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/11/07/predicting-hurricane-evacuation-for-local-neighborhoods-across-a-metropolitan-region/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2212420923005976&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;International Journal of Disaster Risk Reduction&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; To mitigate the devastating impacts of hurricanes on people&amp;rsquo;s lives, communities, and societal infrastructures, disaster management would benefit considerably from a detailed understanding of evacuation, including the socio-demographics of the populations that evacuate, or remain, down to disaggregated geographic levels such as local neighborhoods. A detailed household evacuation prediction model for local neighborhoods requires both a robust household evacuation decision model and individual household data for small geographic units. This paper utilizes a recently published statistical meta-analysis for the first requirement and then conducts a rigorous population synthesis procedure for the second. Our model produces predicted non-evacuation rates for all US Census block groups for the Tampa-St. Petersburg-Clearwater Metropolitan Statistical Area for a Hurricane Irma-like storm along with their socio-demographic and hurricane impact risk profiles. Our model predictions indicate that non-evacuation rates are likely to vary considerably, even across neighboring block groups, driven by the variability in evacuation risk profiles. Our results also demonstrate how different predictors may come to the fore in influencing non-evacuation in different block groups, and that predictors which may have an outsize impact on individual household evacuation decisions, such as Race, are not necessarily associated with the greatest differentials in non-evacuation rates when we aggregate households to block group level and above. Our research is intended to provide a framework for the design of hurricane evacuation prediction tools that could be used in disaster management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu guest-edits the &#34;Sustainable transportation and mobility solutions&#34; collection in Scientific Reports</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/10/11/dr-yujie-hu-guest-edits-the-sustainable-transportation-and-mobility-solutions-collection-in-scientific-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/10/11/dr-yujie-hu-guest-edits-the-sustainable-transportation-and-mobility-solutions-collection-in-scientific-reports/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu serves as a guest editor for the &#34;Sustainable transportation and mobility solutions&#34; collection in the journal &lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Research into sustainable transportation and mobility solutions can help to reduce the negative environmental and social impacts associated with current transportation systems. Key factors are the promotion of energy efficiency, emission reduction, and improved accessibility. Intelligent transportation systems and smart city technologies are utilized to optimize traffic flow and reduce congestion. Increased reliance on public transportation rather than private methods, policies aiming to encourage active modes of transport (such as walking or cycling) and use of low-emission vehicles in place of older high-emission machines help to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and improve the quality of life for communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations to our 2023 graduates!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/08/04/congratulations-to-our-graduates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/08/04/congratulations-to-our-graduates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We wanted to congratulate our lab members who recently graduated: Cade Gouin on getting a Master&#39;s Degree in Geography and Finn Rimay on getting his Bachelors degree in Microbiology and Cell Science and graduating Summa Cum Laude with highest distinction!&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NSF grant to study human movement dynamics under hurricane threats</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/08/04/new-nsf-grant-to-study-human-movement-dynamics-under-hurricane-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/08/04/new-nsf-grant-to-study-human-movement-dynamics-under-hurricane-threats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu and collaborators Dr. Leo Duan and Dr.  George Michailidis have received a new grant from the National Science Foundation to conduct geospatial modeling and risk mitigation for human movement dynamics under hurricane threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More information about the project can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nsf.gov/awardsearch/showAward?AWD_ID=2319551&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian inference using the proximal mapping: Uncertainty quantification under varying dimensionality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/07/10/bayesian-inference-using-the-proximal-mapping-uncertainty-quantification-under-varying-dimensionality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/07/10/bayesian-inference-using-the-proximal-mapping-uncertainty-quantification-under-varying-dimensionality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/01621459.2023.2220170&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of the American Statistical Association&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; In statistical applications, it is common to encounter parameters supported on a varying or unknown dimensional space. Examples include the fused lasso regression, the matrix recovery under an unknown low rank, etc. Despite the ease of obtaining a point estimate via optimization, it is much more challenging to quantify their uncertainty. In the Bayesian framework, a major difficulty is that if assigning the prior associated with a p-dimensional measure, then there is zero posterior probability on any lower-dimensional subset with dimension d &amp;lt; p. To avoid this caveat, one needs to choose another dimension-selection prior on d, which often involves a highly combinatorial problem. To significantly reduce the modeling burden, we propose a new generative process for the prior: starting from a continuous random variable such as multivariate Gaussian, we transform it into a varying-dimensional space using the proximal mapping. This leads to a large class of new Bayesian models that can directly exploit the popular frequentist regularizations and their algorithms, such as the nuclear norm penalty and the alternating direction method of multipliers, while providing a principled and probabilistic uncertainty estimation. We show that this framework is well justified in the geometric measure theory, and enjoys a convenient posterior computation via the standard Hamiltonian Monte Carlo. We demonstrate its use in the analysis of the dynamic flow network data. Supplementary materials for this article are available online.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu joins the Editorial Board of Scientific Reports</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/30/dr-yujie-hu-joins-the-editorial-board-of-scientific-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/30/dr-yujie-hu-joins-the-editorial-board-of-scientific-reports/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu joins the Editorial Board of &lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt; is an open access journal publishing original research from across all areas of the natural sciences, psychology, medicine and engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More details about the journal can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nature.com/srep/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu talks about commuting in the age of rising costs with WUSF Public Media</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/02/13/dr-yujie-hu-talks-about-commuting-in-the-age-of-rising-costs-with-wusf-public-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/02/13/dr-yujie-hu-talks-about-commuting-in-the-age-of-rising-costs-with-wusf-public-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu was featured on the latest coverage &lt;a href=&#34;https://wusfnews.wusf.usf.edu/local-state/2023-02-13/lack-of-affordable-homes-means-longer-commute-times-for-more-people-in-the-tampa-metro-area&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Lack of affordable homes means longer commute times for more people in the Tampa metro area&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a class=&#34;Link&#34; href=&#34;https://wusfnews.wusf.usf.edu/gabriella-paul&#34; aria-label=&#34;Gabriella Paul&#34;&gt;Gabriella Paul&lt;/a&gt; at WUSF News.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read the coverage &lt;a href=&#34;https://wusfnews.wusf.usf.edu/local-state/2023-02-13/lack-of-affordable-homes-means-longer-commute-times-for-more-people-in-the-tampa-metro-area&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- wp:embed {&#34;url&#34;:&#34;https://twitter.com/GabriellaPaul8/status/1625247846806044673&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;rich&#34;,&#34;providerNameSlug&#34;:&#34;twitter&#34;,&#34;responsive&#34;:true} --&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;https://twitter.com/GabriellaPaul8/status/1625247846806044673&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;!-- /wp:embed --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu joins the Editorial Board of Computers, Environment and Urban Systems</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/16/dr-yujie-hu-joins-the-editorial-board-of-computers-environment-and-urban-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/16/dr-yujie-hu-joins-the-editorial-board-of-computers-environment-and-urban-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu joins the Editorial Board of Computers, Environment and Urban Systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Computers, Environment and Urban Systems&lt;/em&gt; is an interdisciplinary journal publishing cutting-edge and innovative &lt;strong&gt;computer-based research&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;strong&gt;urban systems, systems of cities, and built and natural environments &lt;/strong&gt;, that privileges the &lt;strong&gt;geospatial&lt;/strong&gt; perspective. The journal provides a stimulating presentation of perspectives, research developments, overviews of important new technologies and uses of major computational, information-based, and visualization innovations. Applied and theoretical contributions demonstrate the scope of computer-based analysis fostering a better understanding of urban systems, the synergistic relationships between built and natural environments, their spatial scope and their dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cyclically adjusted spatio-temporal kernel density estimation method for predictive crime hotspot analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/11/a-cyclically-adjusted-spatio-temporal-kernel-density-estimation-method-for-predictive-crime-hotspot-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/01/11/a-cyclically-adjusted-spatio-temporal-kernel-density-estimation-method-for-predictive-crime-hotspot-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/19475683.2023.2166584&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Annals of GIS&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; This paper presents a new method for predictive crime hotspot analysis that further improves the kernel density estimation (KDE) method and the spatio-temporal kernel density estimation (STKDE) method by accounting for temporal crime cycles and is therefore termed the ‘cyclically adjusted STKDE (cSTKDE) method’. The case study on robbery incidents in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, shows a temporal cycle with a 6-month period of statistical significance from January 2010 to May 2018. This identified period is incorporated into the temporal kernel function of the new cSTKDE method. For validation, the Forecast Accuracy Index (FAI) and Forecast Precision Index (FPI) are used to evaluate the performance across 52 weeks in 2013. For 11 consecutive weeks since the beginning of 2013, the cSTKDE method outperforms the STKDE by 89% lower average abs(1-FAI) and 17% higher average FPI, and outperforms the KDE by 90% lower average abs(1-FAI) and 8% higher average FPI. Overall, the scenario with the best predictive accuracy by the cSTKDE is recommended over the traditional KDE or STKDE method as most feasible and effective in implementation of hotspot policing in practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying critical transfer zones to coordinate transit with on-demand services using crowdsourced trajectory data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/21/identifying-critical-transfer-zones-to-coordinate-transit-with-on-demand-services-using-crowdsourced-trajectory-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/21/identifying-critical-transfer-zones-to-coordinate-transit-with-on-demand-services-using-crowdsourced-trajectory-data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear: both&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/15472450.2022.2132389&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Intelligent Transportation Systems&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; This study develops a data-driven approach for identifying critical transfer zones in the city to facilitate the coordination of transit and emerging on-demand services. First, the methods convert the trajectories into a 3 D grid with an optimal cube size. Built upon that, we zoom in and study the trajectory density of each mode in a cube and present the results by heatmaps. After that, we zoom out and aggregate those cube information fragments through the clustering algorithms to explore two critical patterns: the ridesharing swarm (RS) zones where many ridesharing trips go through, and the “sandwich pattern” zones where a transit trajectory dominant zone is sandwiched by two ridesharing trajectory dominant zones. Our numerical analysis confirms that these RS zones are well correlated to the promising areas/corridors for integrating transit and on-demand services; the “sandwich patterns” help discover first/last mile (FLM) zones. Last, we further develop a two-channel deep learning network to predict the variation of the FLM gaps so that adaptive services can be planned. A case study based on the field data of the second ring region of Chengdu, China confirms the effectiveness and capability of our analysis approach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood divides: Where you live matters for commuting and its efficiency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/11/neighborhood-divides-where-you-live-matters-for-commuting-and-its-efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/11/neighborhood-divides-where-you-live-matters-for-commuting-and-its-efficiency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0264275122005303&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Cities&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Excess commuting reflects a cits overall commuting efficiency by quantifying the proportion of non-optimal commute that would be avoided if resident workers could freely swap houses or jobs in a given urban form. This framework has been widely used to evaluate urban land use and transportation policy decision-makings. One major methodological limitation in the excess commuting literature is that most existing studies establish on an oversimplified assumption of homogeneous resident workers/jobs, which neglects the complexity of residential (and employment) location choices. To fill this gap, this research develops a methodology to measure excess commuting across worker subgroups differentiated by residential neighborhood type, which captures the comprehensive socioeconomic profiles of workers defined based on multiple attributes. Based on a cross-sectional study of Portland, Boston, New Orleans, and Detroit, it is found that the traditional method overestimates the commuting benchmarks and causes biased evaluation of commuting efficiency performance. Moreover, this research reveals significant disparities in excess commuting across different neighborhood types and identifies three representative subgroups of distinct excess commuting patterns, which are the traditional suburban subgroup, new starts subgroup, and socioeconomically disadvantaged subgroup. With this proposed methodology, more effective and heterogeneous policies targeting different population subgroups could be developed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delineating and comparing local labor market geographies of Millennials, Generation Xers, and Baby Boomers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/05/delineating-and-comparing-local-labor-market-geographies-of-millennials-generation-xers-and-baby-boomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/11/05/delineating-and-comparing-local-labor-market-geographies-of-millennials-generation-xers-and-baby-boomers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2214367X22001193&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Travel Behaviour and Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; There has been an increasing share of older workers in America’s workforce as Baby Boomers continue to age into this group. This raises questions about what their local labor markets look like in space and how they differ from Millennials and Generation Xers who are also active in today’s workforce. However, even though significant generational (or age) differences in commuting distance have been well documented, questions about generational disparities in local labor market geographies have not been investigated. Although several definitions of market areas exist, they were delineated using all commuting trips made by all workers in a region and thus may not be representative of subgroups of workers. The aim of this research is to delineate generation-specific local labor market areas and compare how they differ from one another. Using flow visualizations and three employment self-containment indices applied to a Longitudinal Employer-Household Dynamics dataset of Florida, this research finds that the core-based statistical areas, a popular definition of local labor market areas, understate the true market geographies across generational cohorts. It then delineates generation-specific market areas using a popular community detection method and compares their geographies using the self-containment indices. Results demonstrate largely consistent market geographies across the three generational cohorts in most regions in Florida. Most of these consistent market areas encompass two or more metros, indicating the emergence of functional megaregions centering on major metropolitan hubs. Substantial generational differences in market geographies do exist and concentrate in regions appealing to seniors along the Gulf of Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the retail food environment index (RFEI) with neighborhood commuting patterns: A hybrid human−environment measure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/30/enhancing-the-retail-food-environment-index-rfei-with-neighborhood-commuting-patterns-a-hybrid-human%e2%88%92environment-measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/30/enhancing-the-retail-food-environment-index-rfei-with-neighborhood-commuting-patterns-a-hybrid-human%e2%88%92environment-measure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mdpi.com/1660-4601/19/17/10798&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; The Retail Food Environment Index (RFEI) and its variants have been widely used in public health to measure people’s accessibility to healthy food. These indices are purely environmental as they only concern the geographic distribution of food retailers, but fail to include human factors, such as demographics, socio-economy, and mobility, which also shape the food environment. The exclusion of human factors limits the explanatory power of RFEIs in identifying neighborhoods of the greatest concern. In this study, we first proposed a hybrid approach to integrate human and environmental factors into the RFEI. We then demonstrated this approach by incorporating neighborhood commuting patterns into a traditional RFEI: we devised a multi-origin RFEI (MO_RFEI) that allows people to access food from both homes and workplaces, and further an enhanced RFEI (eRFEI) that allows people to access food with different transportation modes. We compared the traditional and proposed RFEIs in a case study of Florida, USA, and found that the eRFEI identified fewer and more clustered underserved populations, allowing policymakers to intervene more effectively. The eRFEI depicts more realistic human shopping behaviors and better represents the food environment. Our study enriches the literature by offering a new and generic approach for assimilating a neighborhood context into food environment measures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilience and fragmentation in healthcare coalitions: The link between resource contributions and centrality in health-related interorganizational networks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/25/resilience-and-fragmentation-in-healthcare-coalitions-the-link-between-resource-contributions-and-centrality-in-health-related-interorganizational-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/25/resilience-and-fragmentation-in-healthcare-coalitions-the-link-between-resource-contributions-and-centrality-in-health-related-interorganizational-networks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0378873322000624&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Social Networks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Interorganizational coalitions or collaboratives in healthcare are essential to address the health challenges of local communities, particularly during crises such as the Covid-19 pandemic. However, few studies use large-scale data to systematically assess the network structure of these collaboratives and understand their potential to be resilient or fragment in the face of structural changes. This paper analyzes data collected in 2009–2017 about 817 organizations (nodes) in 42 healthcare collaboratives (networks) throughout Florida, the third-largest U.S. state by population, including information about interorganizational ties and organizations’ resource contributions to their coalitions. Social network methods are used to characterize the resilience of these collaboratives, including identification of key players through various centrality metrics, analyses of fragmentation centrality and core/periphery structure, and Exponential Random &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about Graph Models from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/mathematics/graph-model&#34;&gt;Graph Models&lt;/a&gt; to examine how resource contributions facilitate interorganizational ties. Results show that the most significant resource contributions are made by key players identified through fragmentation centrality and by members of the network core. Departure or removal of these organizations would both strongly disrupt network structure and sever essential resource contributions, undermining the overall resilience of a collaborative. Furthermore, one-third of collaboratives are highly susceptible to disruption if any fragmentation-central organization is removed. More fragmented networks are also associated with poorer health-system outcomes in domains such as education, health policy, and services. ERGMs reveal that two types of resource contributions – community connections and in-kind resource sharing – are especially important to facilitate the formation of interorganizational ties in these coalitions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-based movement recognition reveals badminton player footwork using deep learning and binocular positioning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/22/vision-based-movement-recognition-reveals-badminton-player-footwork-using-deep-learning-and-binocular-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/08/22/vision-based-movement-recognition-reveals-badminton-player-footwork-using-deep-learning-and-binocular-positioning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2405844022013779&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Heliyon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Coordinating dynamic interceptive actions in sports like badminton requires skilled performance in getting the racket into the right place at the right time. For this reason, the strategic movement and placement of one&amp;rsquo;s feet, or &lt;em&gt;footwork&lt;/em&gt;, is an important part of competitive performance. Developing an automated, efficient, and economical method to record individual movement characteristics of players is critical and can benefit athletes and motor control specialists. Here, we propose new methods for recording data on the footwork of individual badminton players, in which deep learning is used to obtain image coordinates (2D) of their shoes and binocular positioning to reconstruct the 3D coordinates of the shoes. Results show that the final positioning accuracy is 74.7%. Using the proposed methods, we revealed inter-individual adaptations in the footwork of several participants during competitive performance. The data provided insights on how individual participants coordinated footwork to intercept the &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about projectile from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/earth-and-planetary-sciences/projectile&#34;&gt;projectile&lt;/a&gt;, by varying the distance traveled on court and jump height. Compared with visual observations by &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about biomechanists from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/biomechanist&#34;&gt;biomechanists&lt;/a&gt; and motor control specialists, the proposed methods can obtain quantitative data, provide analysis and evaluation of each participant&amp;rsquo;s performance, revealing personal characteristics that could be targeted to shape the individualized training programs of players to refine their badminton footwork.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating grocery delivery hubs for food deserts at local convenience stores via spatial and temporal consolidation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/04/07/creating-grocery-delivery-hubs-for-food-deserts-at-local-convenience-stores-via-spatial-and-temporal-consolidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/04/07/creating-grocery-delivery-hubs-for-food-deserts-at-local-convenience-stores-via-spatial-and-temporal-consolidation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0038012122000866&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Socio-Economic Planning Sciences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; For many socioeconomically disadvantaged customers living in food deserts, the high costs and minimum order size requirements make attended grocery deliveries financially non-viable, although it has a potential to provide healthy foods to the food insecure population. This paper proposes consolidating customer orders and delivering to a neighborhood convenience store instead of home delivery. We employ an optimization framework involving the minimum cost set covering and the capacitated &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about vehicle routing problems from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/economics-econometrics-and-finance/vehicle-routing-problem&#34;&gt;vehicle routing problems&lt;/a&gt;. Our experimental studies in three counties in the U.S. suggest that by spatial and temporal consolidation of orders, the deliverer can remove minimum order-size requirements and reduce the delivery costs, depending on various factors, compared to attended home-delivery. We find the number and size of time windows for home delivery to be the most important factor in achieving temporal consolidation benefits. Other significant factors in achieving spatial consolidation include the capacity of delivery vehicles, the number of depots, and the number of customer orders. We also find that the number of partner convenience stores and the walkable distance parameter of the model have a significant impact on the number of accepted orders, i.e., the service level provided by the deliverer. The findings of this study imply consolidated grocery delivery as a viable solution to improve fresh food access in food deserts. In light of the recent global pandemic and its exacerbating effects on food insecurity, the innovative solution proposed in this paper is even more relevant and timely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unequal commuting efficiency: A visual analytics approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2022/03/30/the-unequal-commuting-efficiency-a-visual-analytics-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2022/03/30/the-unequal-commuting-efficiency-a-visual-analytics-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Transport Geography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Excess &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about commuting from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/social-sciences/commuting&#34;&gt;commuting&lt;/a&gt; measures commuting efficiency by comparing the actual commute with minimum commute for a given urban form (&lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515#bb0015&#34; name=&#34;bbb0015&#34;&gt;Hu and Li, 2021&lt;/a&gt;). Despite recent methodological advances, research gaps still exist. Calculating the minimum commute requires an optimization process of swapping residences/jobs among workers (&lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515#bb0045&#34; name=&#34;bbb0045&#34;&gt;White, 1988&lt;/a&gt;), and many commuter disaggregation approaches have been proposed for more meaningful estimates. This includes the disaggregation by occupation type, income, age, and other socioeconomic characteristics or travel behaviors (e.g., &lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515#bb0010&#34; name=&#34;bbb0010&#34;&gt;Horner et al., 2015&lt;/a&gt; and the references therein; &lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515#bb0040&#34; name=&#34;bbb0040&#34;&gt;Schleith et al., 2016&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692322000515#bb0015&#34; name=&#34;bbb0015&#34;&gt;Hu and Li, 2021&lt;/a&gt;). Nevertheless, most of these disaggregation analyses are only focused on a single socioeconomic class, which alone could be ineffective to capture the complexity of individuals&amp;rsquo; residential (and employment) location choices. Another gap is about the resulting statistic and its demonstration. As a global indicator, excess commuting is largely reported as a single statistic concerning system-wide commuting efficiency, thus failing to capture and &lt;em&gt;visualize&lt;/em&gt; spatial patterns. This research aims to fill these gaps. Specifically, we stratify commuters into distinct subgroups by residential neighborhood types using multiple socioeconomic variables related to residential and employment characteristics and then measure excess commuting across subgroups. Moreover, we create and geovisualize commuting networks associated with the actual, optimal, and excess commuter flow patterns to better reveal the spatial interaction patterns between locations and the disparities across commuter subgroups.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unequal commute: Comparing commuting patterns across income and racial worker subgroups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/12/17/the-unequal-commute-comparing-commuting-patterns-across-income-and-racial-worker-subgroups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/12/17/the-unequal-commute-comparing-commuting-patterns-across-income-and-racial-worker-subgroups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/0308518X211068852&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Environment and Planning A: Economy and Space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; The spatial dimension of the journey-to-work has important implications for land use and development policymaking and has been widely studied. One thrust of this research is concerned with the disaggregation of workers into subgroups for understanding disparities in commute. Most of these studies, however, were limited to the disaggregation by single socioeconomic class. Hence, this research aims to examine commuting disparities across commuter subgroups stratified by two socioeconomic variables—income and race—using a visual analytics approach. By applying the doubly constrained spatial interaction model to the 2014 Longitudinal Employer-Household Dynamics data, this research first synthesizes commuting flows for Downtown Houston workers across income-race subgroups at the tract level in Harris County, Texas, USA. It then uses bivariate choropleth mapping to visualize the spatial distributions of major Downtown Houston commuter neighborhoods by income-race classes, and significant commuting disparities are identified across income-race subgroups. The results highlight the importance of considering income and race simultaneously for commuting research. The visualization could help policymakers clearly identify the unequal commute across worker subgroups and inform policymaking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictors of hurricane evacuation decisions: A meta-analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/12/10/predictors-of-hurricane-evacuation-decisions-a-meta-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/12/10/predictors-of-hurricane-evacuation-decisions-a-meta-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S027249442100195X&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Environmental Psychology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; We systematically review and meta-analyze quantitative prediction models for &lt;a class=&#34;topic-link&#34; title=&#34;Learn more about hurricane from ScienceDirect&#39;s AI-generated Topic Pages&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/social-sciences/cyclones&#34;&gt;hurricane&lt;/a&gt; evacuation decisions. Drawing on data from 33 prediction models and 29,873 households, we estimate distributions of effects on evacuation decisions for 25 predictors. Mobile home occupancy, evacuation orders, and having an evacuation plan showed the largest positive effects on evacuation, whereas increased age and Black race showed the largest negative effects. These results highlight the importance of both social-economic-structural factors and government action, such as evacuation orders, for enabling evacuation behaviors. Moderator analyses showed that models built using real-hurricane decisions showed larger effects than models of hypothetical decisions, especially for the strongest predictors. Additionally, models in Florida had more consistent results than for other U.S. states, and models with a larger number of covariates showed smaller effect sizes than models with fewer covariates. Importantly, our study improves methodologically and inferentially over previous reviews of this literature (Preprint and supplemental materials are available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://psyarxiv.com/d5ktm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://psyarxiv.com/d5ktm&#34;&gt;https://psyarxiv.com/d5ktm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu gave a talk at FSU Geography Colloquium Series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/10/15/dr-yujie-hu-gave-a-talk-at-fsu-geography-colloquium-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/10/15/dr-yujie-hu-gave-a-talk-at-fsu-geography-colloquium-series/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu was invited by Florida State University&amp;rsquo;s Geography Department to present his research on constructing optimal geographic units for health care markets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling and Analysis of Excess Commuting with Trip Chains</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/01/04/modeling-and-analysis-of-excess-commuting-with-trip-chains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/01/04/modeling-and-analysis-of-excess-commuting-with-trip-chains/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/24694452.2020.1835461&#34;&gt;Annals of the American Association of Geographers&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1080/24694452.2020.1835461&#34;&gt;10.1080/24694452.2020.1835461&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Commuting, like other types of human travel, is complex in nature, such as trip-chaining behavior involving making stops of multiple purposes between two anchors. According to the 2001 National Household Travel Survey, about half of weekday U.S. workers made a stop during their commute. In excess commuting studies that examine a region’s overall commuting efficiency, commuting is, however, simplified as nonstop travel from homes to jobs. This research fills this gap by proposing a trip-chaining-based model to integrate trip-chaining behavior into excess commuting. Based on a case study of the Tampa Bay region of Florida, this research finds that traditional excess commuting studies underestimate both actual and optimal commute and overestimate excess commuting. For chained commuting trips alone, for example, the mean minimum commute time is increased by 70 percent from 5.48 minutes to 9.32 minutes after trip-chaining is accounted for. The gaps are found to vary across trip-chaining types by a disaggregate analysis by types of chain activities. Hence, policymakers and planners are cautioned with regards to omitting trip-chaining behavior in making urban transportation and land use policies. In addition, the proposed model can be adopted to study the efficiency of nonwork travel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Perception bias”: Deciphering a mismatch between urban crime and perception of safety</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/12/17/perception-bias-deciphering-a-mismatch-between-urban-crime-and-perception-of-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/12/17/perception-bias-deciphering-a-mismatch-between-urban-crime-and-perception-of-safety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0169204620314870&#34;&gt;Landscape and Urban Planning&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2020.104003&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.landurbplan.2020.104003&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Crime and perception of safety are two intertwined concepts affecting the quality of life and the economic development of a society. However, few studies have quantitatively examined the difference between the two due to the lack of granular data documenting public perceptions in a given geographic context. Here, by applying a pre-trained scene understanding algorithm, we infer the perception of safety score of streetscapes for census block groups in the city of Houston using a large number of Google Street View images. Then, using this inferred perception of safety, we create “perception bias” categories for each census block group. These categories capture the level of mismatch between people’s visually perceived safety and the actual crime rates. This measure provides scalable guidance in deciphering the relationship between the built environment and crime. Finally, we construct a series of models to examine the “perception bias” with static and dynamic urban factors, including socioeconomic features (e.g., unemployment rate and ethnic compositions), urban diversity (e.g., number and diversity of Points of Interest), and urban livelihood (i.e., hourly count of visitors). Analytical and numerical results suggest that the association between characteristics of urban space and “perception bias” over crime could be paradoxical. On the one hand, neighborhoods with a higher volume of day-time visitors appear more likely to be safer than it looks (low crime rate and low safety score). On the other hand, those with a higher volume of night-time visitors are likely to be more dangerous than it looks (high crime rate). The findings add further knowledge to the long-recognized relationship between built environment and crime as well as highlight the perception of safety in cities, which in turn enhances our capacity to design urban management strategies that prevent the emergence of extreme “perception bias”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu presented at UFII COVID-19 SEED Awardees Virtual Seminar Series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/12/04/dr-yujie-hu-presented-at-ufii-covid-19-seed-awardees-virtual-seminar-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/12/04/dr-yujie-hu-presented-at-ufii-covid-19-seed-awardees-virtual-seminar-series/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu was invited by UF Informatics Institute to present some preliminary findings from his funded project examining the impacts of COVID-19 on crime patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://informatics.research.ufl.edu/geography-professor-studies-correlation-between-crime-rates-covid-19-in-2020/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for a brief summary of the results and &lt;a href=&#34;https://informatics.research.ufl.edu/aiovg_videos/ufii-covid-19-seed-awardees-virtual-seminar-series-dr-yujie-hu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for his presentation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal dynamics of the impact of land use on modal disparity in commuting efficiency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/07/29/temporal-dynamics-of-the-impact-of-land-use-on-modal-disparity-in-commuting-efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/07/29/temporal-dynamics-of-the-impact-of-land-use-on-modal-disparity-in-commuting-efficiency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0198971520302568&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Computers, Environment and Urban Systems&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a class=&#34;doi&#34; title=&#34;Persistent link using digital object identifier&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.compenvurbsys.2020.101523&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; aria-label=&#34;Persistent link using digital object identifier&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.compenvurbsys.2020.101523&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Urban land use is known to affect commuting efficiency according to the excess commuting framework. However, most studies do not include temporal dynamics, and those that do, focus on decadal, yearly, or daily temporal resolutions. However, commuting is not a stationary spatial process. Since people leave home and start their jobs at different times of the day and since traffic congestion varies throughout the day, neglecting hourly dynamics can misestimate commuting efficiency in a region and lead to erroneous policy implications. Another important issue often overlooked in the past is the modal disparity in commuting efficiency and how it evolves during the day. To overcome these limitations, this research examines the commuting efficiency variation by car and public transport by six one-hour periods between 5 AM and 11 AM in Warsaw, Poland, using travel survey data and travel times generated from GPS-based big data for cars and from GTFS for public transport. We develop four different groups of modeling scenarios: no disaggregation, disaggregation by time, disaggregation by mode, and disaggregation by time and mode. Therefore, excess commuting and modal disparity metrics are applied for a total of 21 specific time and mode combinations. The results suggest that commuting efficiency is worst during the 8–9 AM period for both modes, and that public transport users are more efficient after 7 AM. Hourly variations in the excess commuting metrics imply that policy makers should examine ways to encourage flexible work hours to distribute work starts and to increase public transport frequencies in the off-peak.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A tale of two cities: Jobs–housing balance and urban spatial structures from the perspective of transit commuters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/07/10/a-tale-of-two-cities-jobs-housing-balance-and-urban-spatial-structures-from-the-perspective-of-transit-commuters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/07/10/a-tale-of-two-cities-jobs-housing-balance-and-urban-spatial-structures-from-the-perspective-of-transit-commuters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/2399808320938803&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Environment and Planning B: Urban Analytics and City Science&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a class=&#34;doiWidgetLink&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1177%2F2399808320938803&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1177/2399808320938803&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; The jobs–housing balance and urban spatial structure are naturally connected, and understanding the connection is important for urban planning, geography, and transport studies. Using smartcard data in Beijing and Shanghai, this research employs a comparative approach to reveal spatial distribution patterns of jobs–housing balance in terms of transit commuters and derive the implied urban spatial structures for the two megacities in China. Results suggested that (1) the overall job–resident ratios estimated with smartcard data were 1.97 and 2.47 in Shanghai and Beijing, respectively; (2) compared to Beijing, Shanghai had greater intermixing of jobs and housing; (3) Beijing’s urban form followed a concentric spatial structure, whereas Shanghai followed a quasi-sector configuration. These findings show that the job–resident ratio can be used as an indicator to capture land-use patterns or functional zones, which is useful for urban planning and transit network design.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Geographer: Dr. Yujie Hu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/26/meet-the-geographer-dr-yujie-hu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/26/meet-the-geographer-dr-yujie-hu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu was recently interviewed by UF Geography Department about how he got interested in Transportation Geography, networks, and GIS! Thanks to Mike Simonovich for interviewing!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://geog.ufl.edu/2020/06/26/meet-the-geographer-dr-yujie-hu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for more detail.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating a large drive time matrix between ZIP codes in the United States: A differential sampling approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/15/estimating-a-large-drive-time-matrix-between-zip-codes-in-the-united-states-a-differential-sampling-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/15/estimating-a-large-drive-time-matrix-between-zip-codes-in-the-united-states-a-differential-sampling-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692319310051&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Transport Geography&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692319310051&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.jtrangeo.2020.102770&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Estimating a massive drive time matrix between locations is a practical but challenging task. The challenges include availability of reliable road network (including traffic) data, programming expertise, and access to high-performance computing resources. This research proposes a method for estimating a nationwide drive time matrix between ZIP code areas in the U.S.—a geographic unit at which many national datasets including health information are compiled and distributed. The method (1) does not rely on intensive efforts in data preparation or access to advanced computing resources, (2) uses algorithms of varying complexity and computational time to estimate drive times of different trip lengths, and (3) accounts for both interzonal and intrazonal drive times. The core design samples ZIP code pairs with various intensities according to trip lengths and derives the drive times via Google Maps API, and the Google times are then used to adjust and improve some primitive estimates of drive times with low computational costs. The result provides a valuable resource for researchers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu awarded the UFII COVID-19 Response SEED Funding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/12/dr-yujie-hu-awarded-the-ufii-covid-19-response-seed-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/06/12/dr-yujie-hu-awarded-the-ufii-covid-19-response-seed-funding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu is awarded the &lt;a href=&#34;https://informatics.institute.ufl.edu/ufii-programs/seed-funds/covid-19-response-seed-funding/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;COVID-19 Response SEED Funding&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://informatics.institute.ufl.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;UFII&lt;/a&gt; (UF Informatics Institute). This competitive research award provides seed money for applications for data science, machine learning, AI, and mathematical modeling related research that can be rapidly mobilized to help address various facets of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Hu and his collaborator will be examining the impacts of the COVID-19 pandemic on crimes. His team is looking for two student OPS positions (undergrad or grad) to contribute to this project. Refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://geog.ufl.edu/2020/06/17/ops-opportunity-for-socioeconomic-impacts-of-covid-19-a-criminological-perspective/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; for more detail about the positions and how to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility and transportation equity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/04/30/accessibility-and-transportation-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/04/30/accessibility-and-transportation-equity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New editorial published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/12/9/3611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Sustainability&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/12/9/3611&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.3390/su12093611&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this introduction to the Special Issue of Sustainability on accessibility and equity in transportation, we attempt to synthesize key lessons from the issue’s fifteen substantive articles. These involve accessibility-related lessons including accessibility improvement in railways; optimizations of cross-border road accessibility, intercity networks, and pedestrian access to public transportation; as well as various aspects in urban transportation planning such as urban mobility, integration of bike-sharing, and electronically powered personal mobility vehicles. Other lessons cover equity-related aspects of transportation including the provision of the maximally full information to underserved populations to lessen the burden of unequitable access to urban facilities, ensuring socially equitable transportation planning and reducing burdens in commuting cost among low-income commuters. Finally, remaining lessons link equity back to accessibility with discussions on accessibility to public transport for disabled as well as visually impaired people, and equitable job access by poor commuters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating road network accessibility during a hurricane evacuation: A case study of hurricane Irma in Florida</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/04/09/estimating-road-network-accessibility-during-a-hurricane-evacuation-a-case-study-of-hurricane-irma-in-florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/04/09/estimating-road-network-accessibility-during-a-hurricane-evacuation-a-case-study-of-hurricane-irma-in-florida/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1361920919313008&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Transportation Research Part D: Transport and Environment&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1361920919313008&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.trd.2020.102334&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding the spatio-temporal road network accessibility during a hurricane evacuation—the level of ease of residents in an area in reaching evacuation destination sites through the road network—is a critical component of emergency management. While many studies have attempted to measure road accessibility (either in the scope of evacuation or beyond), few have considered both dynamic evacuation demand and characteristics of a hurricane. This study proposes a methodological framework to achieve this goal. In an interval of every six hours, the method first estimates the evacuation demand in terms of number of vehicles per household in each county subdivision (sub-county) by considering the hurricane’s wind radius and track. The closest facility analysis is then employed to model evacuees’ route choices towards the predefined evacuation destinations. The potential crowdedness index (PCI), a metric capturing the level of crowdedness of each road segment, is then computed by coupling the estimated evacuation demand and route choices. Finally, the road accessibility of each sub-county is measured by calculating the reciprocal of the sum of PCI values of corresponding roads connecting evacuees from the sub-county to the designated destinations. The method is applied to the entire state of Florida during Hurricane Irma in September 2017. Results show that I-75 and I-95 northbound have a high level of congestion, and sub-counties along the northbound I-95 suffer from the worst road accessibility. In addition, this research performs a sensitivity analysis for examining the impacts of different choices of behavioral response curves on accessibility results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated delineation of cancer service areas in northeast region of the united states: a network optimization approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2020/03/06/automated-delineation-of-cancer-service-areas-in-northeast-region-of-the-united-states-a-network-optimization-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2020/03/06/automated-delineation-of-cancer-service-areas-in-northeast-region-of-the-united-states-a-network-optimization-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1877584520300162&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Spatial and Spatio-temporal Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1877584520300162&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.sste.2020.100338&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Objective&#xA;Derivation of service areas is an important methodology for evaluating healthcare variation, which can be refined to more robust, condition-specific, and empirically-based automated regions, using cancer service areas as an exemplar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data sources/study setting&#xA;Medicare claims (2014–2015) for the nine-state Northeast region were used to develop a ZIP-code-level origin-destination matrix for cancer services (surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation). This population-based study followed a utilization-based approach to delineate cancer service areas (CSAs) to develop and test an improved methodology for small area analyses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIS and health</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2019/11/26/gis-and-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2019/11/26/gis-and-health/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New book chapter published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oxfordbibliographies.com/view/document/obo-9780199874002/obo-9780199874002-0211.xml&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Oxford Bibliographies&lt;/a&gt;; DOI:  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oxfordbibliographies.com/view/document/obo-9780199874002/obo-9780199874002-0211.xml&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1093/OBO/9780199874002-0211&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT: &lt;/strong&gt;The capability of GIS to be able to store, retrieve, display, and analyze large quantities of spatially referenced data has facilitated the rapid growth of geographic-based research within various health fields, including epidemiology and health care provisioning. This is reflected in the numerous texts focused entirely on GIS and health, as well as texts focused on geography and health that include substantial material on GIS. There are also journals where GIS-based health research frequently appears. This bibliography lists a number of these texts and journals. GIS-based health research is wide ranging, but several major themes can be identified. In this bibliography the first major theme presented is GIS-based visualization of health information, a topic which involves geocoding, disease-mapping methodologies, and alternative cartographic schemes of representation. The second major theme is GIS-derived measures for health research, where the focus is on how GIS has transformed how accessibility to health care is measured and enabled complex forms of environmental exposures to be derived for use in epidemiologic studies. The final theme is GIS-enabled analysis for health research where a deliberate choice was made to focus on those analytical areas which are only feasible through the specific spatial analytical capabilities of GIS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of coastal hazards on residents’ spatial accessibility to health services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2019/09/30/impact-of-coastal-hazards-on-residents-spatial-accessibility-to-health-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2019/09/30/impact-of-coastal-hazards-on-residents-spatial-accessibility-to-health-services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ascelibrary.org/doi/abs/10.1061/%28ASCE%29IS.1943-555X.0000509?af=R&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Infrastructure Systems&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ascelibrary.org/doi/abs/10.1061/%28ASCE%29IS.1943-555X.0000509?af=R&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1061/(ASCE)IS.1943-555X.0000509&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; The mobility of residents and their access to essential services can be highly affected by transportation network closures that occur during and after coastal hazard events. Few studies have used geographic information systems coupled with infrastructure vulnerability models to explore how spatial accessibility to goods and services shifts after a hurricane. Models that explore spatial accessibility to health services are particularly lacking. This study provides a framework to examine how the disruption of transportation networks during and after a hurricane can impact a resident’s ability to access health services over time. Two different bridge-closure conditions—inundation and structural failure—along with roadway inundation are used to quantify posthurricane accessibility at short- and long-term temporal scales. Inundation may close a bridge for hours or days, but a structural failure may close a route for weeks or months. Both forms of closure are incorporated using probabilistic vulnerability models coupled with GIS-based models to assess spatial accessibility in the aftermath of a coastal hazard. Harris County, an area in southeastern Texas prone to coastal hazards, is used as a case study. The results indicate changes in the accessibility scores of specific areas depending on the temporal scale of interest and intensity of the hazard scenario. Sociodemographic indicators are also examined for the study region, revealing the populations most likely to suffer from lack of accessibility. Overall, the presented framework helps to understand how both short-term functionality loss and long-term damage affect access to critical services such as healthcare after a hazard. This information, in turn, can shape decisions about future mitigation and planning efforts, and the presented framework can be expanded to other hazard-prone areas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Yujie Hu awarded the Ralph E. Powe Junior Faculty Enhancement Awards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2019/08/16/dr-yujie-hu-awarded-the-ralph-e-powe-junior-faculty-enhancement-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2019/08/16/dr-yujie-hu-awarded-the-ralph-e-powe-junior-faculty-enhancement-awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yujie Hu is awarded the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.orau.org/university-partnerships/member-grant-programs/powe/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ralph E. Powe Junior Faculty Enhancement Awards&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.orau.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ORAU&lt;/a&gt; (Oak Ridge Associated Universities). This competitive research award provides seed money for junior faculty members that often result in additional funding from other sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read more at: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.orau.org/university-partnerships/member-grant-programs/powe/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ORAU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining and optimizing the BCycle bike-sharing system – A pilot study in Colorado, US</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2019/04/12/examining-and-optimizing-the-bcycle-bike-sharing-system-a-pilot-study-in-colorado-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2019/04/12/examining-and-optimizing-the-bcycle-bike-sharing-system-a-pilot-study-in-colorado-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0306261919306324&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Applied Energy&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0306261919306324&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.apenergy.2019.04.007&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Many cities around the world have integrated bike-sharing programs into their public transit systems to promise sustainable, affordable transportation and reduce environmental pollution in urban areas. Investigating the usage patterns of shared bikes is of key importance to understand cyclist’s behaviors and subsequently optimize bike-sharing programs. Based on the historical trip records of bike users and station empty/full status data, this paper evaluated and optimized the bike-sharing program BCycle in the city of Boulder, Colorado, the United States, using a combination of different methods including the Potential Path Area (PPA) and the Capacitated Maximal Covering Location Problem (CMCLP). Results showed significantly different usage patterns between membership groups, revealed diverse imbalance patterns of bike supply and demand across stations in the city and provided three system upgrading strategies about maximizing the service coverage. This case study is committed to future energy conservation and sustainable energy systems nationwide and ultimately worldwide, by holding immerse potential to adapt the resulting optimization strategies to the cities with a similar urban context across the United States, as well as more emerging bike-sharing programs in other countries, such as China.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and visualizing place-based space-time job accessibility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/12/15/measuring-and-visualizing-place-based-space-time-job-accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/12/15/measuring-and-visualizing-place-based-space-time-job-accessibility/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692318305994&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Journal of Transport Geography&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692318305994&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.jtrangeo.2018.12.002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Place-based accessibility measures, such as the gravity-based model, are widely applied to study the spatial accessibility of workers to job opportunities in cities. However, gravity-based measures often suffer from three main limitations: (1) they are sensitive to the spatial configuration and scale of the units of analysis, which are not specifically designed for capturing job accessibility patterns and are often too coarse; (2) they omit the temporal dynamics of job opportunities and workers in the calculation, instead assuming that they remain stable over time; and (3) they do not lend themselves to dynamic geovisualization techniques. In this paper, a new methodological framework for measuring and visualizing place-based job accessibility in space and time is presented that overcomes these three limitations. First, discretization and dasymetric mapping approaches are used to disaggregate counts of jobs and workers over specific time intervals to a fine-scale grid. Second, &lt;a class=&#34;workspace-trigger&#34; href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0966692318305994#bb0280&#34; name=&#34;bbb0280&#34;&gt;Shen&amp;rsquo;s (1998)&lt;/a&gt; gravity-based accessibility measure is modified to account for temporal fluctuations in the spatial distributions of the supply of jobs and the demand of workers and is used to estimate hourly job accessibility at each cell. Third, a four-dimensional volumetric rendering approach is employed to integrate the hourly job access estimates into a space-time cube environment, which enables the users to interactively visualize the space-time job accessibility patterns. The integrated framework is demonstrated in the context of a case study of the Tampa Bay region of Florida. The findings demonstrate the value of the proposed methodology in job accessibility analysis and the policy-making process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIS-based simulation and analysis of intra-urban commuting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/11/22/gis-based-simulation-and-analysis-of-intra-urban-commuting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/11/22/gis-based-simulation-and-analysis-of-intra-urban-commuting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New book published: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.routledge.com/GIS-Based-Simulation-and-Analysis-of-Intra-Urban-Commuting/Hu-Wang/p/book/9780367023034?utm_source=crcpress.com&amp;utm_medium=referral&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CRC Press&lt;/a&gt;; ISBN 9780367023034&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Commuting, the daily link between residences and workplaces, sets up the complex interaction between the two most important land uses (residential and employment) in a city, and dictates the configuration of urban structure. In addition to prolonged time and stress for individual commuters on traffic, commuting comes with additional societal costs including elevated crash risks, worsening air quality, and louder traffic noise, etc. These issues are important to city planners, policy researchers, and decision makers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A spatio-temporal kernel density estimation framework for predictive crime hotspot mapping and evaluation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/08/23/a-spatio-temporal-kernel-density-estimation-framework-for-predictive-crime-hotspot-mapping-and-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/08/23/a-spatio-temporal-kernel-density-estimation-framework-for-predictive-crime-hotspot-mapping-and-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0143622818300560?via%3Dihub&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Applied Geography&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0143622818300560?via%3Dihub&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.apgeog.2018.08.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Predictive hotspot mapping plays a critical role in hotspot policing. Existing methods such as the popular kernel density estimation (KDE) do not consider the temporal dimension of crime. Building upon recent works in related fields, this article proposes a spatio-temporal framework for predictive hotspot mapping and evaluation. Comparing to existing work in this scope, the proposed framework has four major features: (1) a spatio-temporal kernel density estimation (STKDE) method is applied to include the temporal component in predictive hotspot mapping, (2) a data-driven optimization technique, the likelihood cross-validation, is used to select the most appropriate bandwidths, (3) a statistical significance test is designed to filter out false positives in the density estimates, and (4) a new metric, the predictive accuracy index (PAI) curve, is proposed to evaluate predictive hotspots at multiple areal scales. The framework is illustrated in a case study of residential burglaries in Baton Rouge, Louisiana in 2011, and the results validate its utility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are the dangerous intersections for pedestrians and cyclists: A colocation-based approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/08/06/where-are-the-dangerous-intersections-for-pedestrians-and-cyclists-a-colocation-based-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/08/06/where-are-the-dangerous-intersections-for-pedestrians-and-cyclists-a-colocation-based-approach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0968090X18307526&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0968090X18307526&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1016/j.trc.2018.07.030&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding the spatio-temporal road network accessibility during a hurricane evacuation—the level of ease of residents in an area in reaching evacuation destination sites through the road network—is a critical component of emergency management. While many studies have attempted to measure road accessibility (either in the scope of evacuation or beyond), few have considered both dynamic evacuation demand and characteristics of a hurricane. This study proposes a methodological framework to achieve this goal. In an interval of every six hours, the method first estimates the evacuation demand in terms of number of vehicles per household in each county subdivision (sub-county) by considering the hurricane’s wind radius and track. The closest facility analysis is then employed to model evacuees’ route choices towards the predefined evacuation destinations. The potential crowdedness index (PCI), a metric capturing the level of crowdedness of each road segment, is then computed by coupling the estimated evacuation demand and route choices. Finally, the road accessibility of each sub-county is measured by calculating the reciprocal of the sum of PCI values of corresponding roads connecting evacuees from the sub-county to the designated destinations. The method is applied to the entire state of Florida during Hurricane Irma in September 2017. Results show that I-75 and I-95 northbound have a high level of congestion, and sub-counties along the northbound I-95 suffer from the worst road accessibility. In addition, this research performs a sensitivity analysis for examining the impacts of different choices of behavioral response curves on accessibility results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated delineation of hospital service areas and hospital referral regions by modularity optimization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2018/02/01/automated-delineation-of-hospital-service-areas-and-hospital-referral-regions-by-modularity-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2018/02/01/automated-delineation-of-hospital-service-areas-and-hospital-referral-regions-by-modularity-optimization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New article first published online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1475-6773.12616&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Health Services Research&lt;/a&gt;; DOI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1475-6773.12616&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1111/1475-6773.12616&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Objective&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To develop an automated, data‐driven, and scale‐flexible method to delineate hospital service areas (HSA s) and hospital referral regions (HRR s) that are up‐to‐date, representative of all patients, and have the optimal localization of hospital visits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data Sources&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2011 state inpatient database in Florida from the Healthcare Cost and Utilization Project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Study Design&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A network optimization method was used to redefine HSA s and HRR s by maximizing patient‐to‐hospital flows within each HSA /HRR while minimizing flows between them. We first constructed as many HSA s/HRR s as existing Dartmouth units in Florida, and then compared the two by various metrics. Next, we sought to derive the optimal numbers and configurations of HSA s/HRR s that best reflect the modularity of hospitalization patterns in Florida.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
